{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756189795","data":{"timestamp":" 947756189795"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756190741","data":{"timestamp":" 947756190741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756191843","data":{"timestamp":" 947756191843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756193403","data":{"timestamp":" 947756193403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756199246","data":{"timestamp":" 947756199245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756206950","data":{"timestamp":" 947756206950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756208297","data":{"timestamp":" 947756208297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_jo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756215613","data":{"timestamp":" 947756215613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756219888","data":{"timestamp":" 947756219888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_lo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756227881","data":{"timestamp":" 947756227881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_gu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756230554","data":{"timestamp":" 947756230554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_gu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756235604","data":{"timestamp":" 947756235604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_gu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756239855","data":{"timestamp":" 947756239855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_gu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756251095","data":{"timestamp":" 947756251095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_za"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756259847","data":{"timestamp":" 947756259847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_za"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756263766","data":{"timestamp":" 947756263766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_za"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756275145","data":{"timestamp":" 947756275145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756276628","data":{"timestamp":" 947756276628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756283986","data":{"timestamp":" 947756283986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756285294","data":{"timestamp":" 947756285294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756293438","data":{"timestamp":" 947756293438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ne"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756294646","data":{"timestamp":" 947756294646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ne"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756304891","data":{"timestamp":" 947756304891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ju"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756306367","data":{"timestamp":" 947756306367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ju"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756315724","data":{"timestamp":" 947756315724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756317351","data":{"timestamp":" 947756317351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756321953","data":{"timestamp":" 947756321953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756329168","data":{"timestamp":" 947756329168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756335290","data":{"timestamp":" 947756335290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756348403","data":{"timestamp":" 947756348403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756355289","data":{"timestamp":" 947756355289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.2ch..2ch..4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756364403","data":{"timestamp":" 947756364402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" e3e18256-556a-49f7-bfc4-a284f9c0f738"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.2ch..2ch..4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756381076","data":{"timestamp":" 947756381075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756381307","data":{"timestamp":" 947756381307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756382283","data":{"timestamp":" 947756382283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756383572","data":{"timestamp":" 947756383571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756386513","data":{"timestamp":" 947756386512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756387369","data":{"timestamp":" 947756387368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756387692","data":{"timestamp":" 947756387692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756388940","data":{"timestamp":" 947756388939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756392544","data":{"timestamp":" 947756392543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756393527","data":{"timestamp":" 947756393527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756393780","data":{"timestamp":" 947756393780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756394736","data":{"timestamp":" 947756394735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756397674","data":{"timestamp":" 947756397674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756398708","data":{"timestamp":" 947756398708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756399181","data":{"timestamp":" 947756399181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756403772","data":{"timestamp":" 947756403771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756403894","data":{"timestamp":" 947756403894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 29ebce0b-5821-4b23-be68-09fd80b1322a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756417056","data":{"timestamp":" 947756417056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bi_bi-fu-ji"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756429655","data":{"timestamp":" 947756429655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_la-po-jo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756437260","data":{"timestamp":" 947756437260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_do_na-do-ro"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756452090","data":{"timestamp":" 947756452090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_zu_zu-no-ba"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zu"," userResponse":" zu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756485797","data":{"timestamp":" 947756485797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hi_ye-fu-hi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hi"," userResponse":" ye"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756491593","data":{"timestamp":" 947756491593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hi_ye-fu-hi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hi"," userResponse":" hi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756507911","data":{"timestamp":" 947756507911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ka_ka-vu-fu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756511484","data":{"timestamp":" 947756511483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ka_ka-vu-fu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756546500","data":{"timestamp":" 947756546500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ka_ka-vu-fu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756574334","data":{"timestamp":" 947756574333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 9254a397-1d8d-4588-a299-d795fe172f1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ka_ka-vu-fu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756594625","data":{"timestamp":" 947756594625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756594856","data":{"timestamp":" 947756594855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756595833","data":{"timestamp":" 947756595832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756597121","data":{"timestamp":" 947756597121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756600028","data":{"timestamp":" 947756600027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756600883","data":{"timestamp":" 947756600882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756601203","data":{"timestamp":" 947756601202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756602446","data":{"timestamp":" 947756602445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756603820","data":{"timestamp":" 947756603820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947756603866","data":{"timestamp":" 947756603866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_123609"," gameId":" 2d563cd5-0d35-4102-a174-100ebd3688a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}